

stolleywilliam@yahoo.com | 9197576496 | Burlington, NC 27215

Summary

Well-organized server with years of experience in customer service and management of guests in both the retail and restaurant industry. Enthusiastic team player, with a strong willingness to do what is asked including going above and beyond. More than successful at multi-tasking and working in an incredibly ever changing fast-paced environment, requiring an even-tempered disposition and the willingness to get the job done, maintaining knowledge of my companies policies.

Skills

- Menu memorization
- Point of Sale (POS) system operations
- Check payment processing
- Wine pairings
- Effective customer upselling

- Regulatory compliance
- Relationship management
- Quality control
- Service prioritization
- Sales Techniques

Experience

Longhorn Steakhouse | Burlington, NC Server

05/2019 - Current

- Educated guests on daily specials and appetizers, entrees, desserts and other menu items.
- Operated POS terminals to input orders, split bills and calculate totals.
- Greeted customers, answered questions and recommended specials, wine and desserts to increase profits.
- Addressed concerns or complaints quickly to improve service and escalated more advanced issues to management for resolution.
- Answered phone inquiries to schedule and confirm reservations, record takeout orders and respond to service questions.

Bonefish Grill | Greensboro, North Carolina

Host

02/2018 - 01/2019

- Supported serving staff, food runners and bussers to keep dining room presentable and ready for guests.
- Scheduled reservations and notified servers and managers of large groups to prepare seating in advance.
- Supported management by resolving customer service and food-related issues to maintain guest satisfaction.

Target | Burlington, North Carolina **Stock Associate** 02/2017 - 12/2017

- Carried out duties within fast-paced retail environment, providing organized stocking methods and plans.
- Assisted customers based on currently available product, promotional and policy information.
- Operated forklift to elevate or place merchandise in appropriate areas.
- Reviewed current planograms and end cap placements to properly merchandise items.
- Prepared products for sales floor by adding tags and readying pallets or restocking.

Education and Training

Leesville Road High School | Raleigh, NC **High School Diploma** 02/2013

University Of North Carolina At Greensboro | Greensboro, NC **Bachelor of Arts** in Music

Accomplishments

- Audition and played in several youth orchestras, including the triangle youth symphony
- Several masterclass sessions, including those alongside famous musicians such as Wynton Marsalis
- Performed with several colleges and performers, including the UNCG jazz ensemble, meredith college symphony, and Molly Ringwald
- Concertmaster for Leesville Road Highschool, involving all the duties required therein